Street & Smith Records
Street & Smith Records
- Films
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_13; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_033_14 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 12-5-5, scene of Margot Lane talking to someone; scene of Margot Lane with Lamont Cranston in his office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_14; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_033_13 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 12-5-5.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_15; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    This is a combined picture reel with two film fragments for street_smith_033_16 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 16A-2-22, scene of Lamont Cranston and Detective Harris talking in Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_16; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    This is a combined sound reel with three separate fragments for street_smith_033_15 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 16A-2-22.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_17; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_033_18 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 10-2-125, scene of a room mirror.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_18; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_033_17 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 10-2-125.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_19; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    This is a combined picture reel with two film fragments for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 17-1-silent, scene of Detective Harris walking into a room.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_20; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a picture reel for street_smith_033_21 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 19C-2-32, scene of Lamont Cranston and Detective Harris talking in Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_21; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a sound reel for street_smith_033_20 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 19C-2-32, scene of Lamont Cranston and Detective Harris talking in Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_22; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a picture reel for street_smith_033_23 for scene of Detective Harris talking to someone.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_23; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a sound reel for street_smith_033_22 for scene of Detective Harris talking to someone.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_24; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a picture reel for street_smith_033_25 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 19-2-28: scene of Lamont Cranston and Detective Harris talking in Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_25; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a sound reel for street_smith_033_24 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 19-2-28.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_26; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 10) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_033_27 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 16-3-70: scene of Lamnot Cranston talking to Commissioner Weston.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (10-19 from CC 854, Take 2), 03/05/1954; street_smith_033_27; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 10) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_033_26 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 16-3-70, fragments might not be in order.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_01; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 5) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_041_02, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 107A-1-143; scene of Margot Lane talking to someone.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_02; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 5) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_041_01, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 107A-1-143.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_03; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 105A-2-silent; scene of a hand holding the photograph of the murder victim.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_04; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 6) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_041_05, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 107B-1-144; scene of Margot Lane talking to Detective Harris and him holding a gun.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_05; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 5) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_041_04, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 107B-1-144.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_06; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 7) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_041_07, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 105-5-46; scene of Landlady talking to Lamont Cranston.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_07; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 7) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_041_06, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 105-5-46.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_08; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 100A-1-116; murder scene with a chalk drawing of the victim's body.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_09; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_041_10, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 104A-1-115; scene of Detective Harris.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_10; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_041_09, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 104A-1-115.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_11; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 6) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_041_12, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 108B-3-148[?]; scene of Detective Harris leaning against a door, looking scared.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_12; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 6) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_041_11, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 108B-3-148[?].
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_13; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_041_14, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 101-7-123; scene of Margot Lane and Detective Harris arguing and Detective Harris pointing a gun at Margot Lane, not letting her leave through the door.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_14; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_041_13, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 101-7-123.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_15; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 100-2-silent; scene of Margot Lane in the victim's apartment.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_16; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 3) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_041_17, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 107-4-142; scene of Margot Lane and Detective Harris talking.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-108 from CC 854, take 4), 01/15/1954; street_smith_041_17; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 3) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a sound reel for street_smith_041_16, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 107-4-142.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-119 from CC 869, take 3), 03/08/1954; street_smith_042_01; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_042_02, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 107B-2-145; scene of Margot Lane in the victim's apartment.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-119 from CC 869, take 3), 03/08/1954; street_smith_042_02; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_042_01, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 107B-2-145; note at the end: "sound for Reel 8".
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-119 from CC 869, take 3), 03/08/1954; street_smith_042_03; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 6) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_042_04, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 108-1-149; scene of Detective Harris looking scared.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-119 from CC 869, take 3), 03/08/1954; street_smith_042_04; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 6) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_042_03, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 108-1-149.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-119 from CC 869, take 3), 03/08/1954; street_smith_042_05; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a picture reel for street_smith_042_06, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 111-2[?]; scene of Lamont Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-119 from CC 869, take 3), 03/08/1954; street_smith_042_06; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a sound reel for street_smith_042_05, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 111-2[?].
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-119 from CC 869, take 3), 03/08/1954; street_smith_042_07; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a picture reel for street_smith_042_08, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 111-2-137; scene of a door.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (100-119 from CC 869, take 3), 03/08/1954; street_smith_042_08; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a sound reel for street_smith_042_07, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 111-2-137.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_01; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_034_02 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 21-2-36: scene of Lamont Cranston talking to Detective Harris in Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_02; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_034_01 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 21-2-36.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_03; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a picture reel for street_smith_034_04 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number: 20A-[?]-[?], scene of Lamont Cranston talking to Detective Harris in Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_04; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a sound reel for street_smith_034_03 for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 20A-[?]-[?],
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_05; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 8) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_034_06, scene of Lamont Cranston and Detective Harris.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_06; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 8) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_034_05.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_07; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a picture reel for street_smith_034_08, scene of Lamont Cranston.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_08; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 2) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a sound reel for street_smith_034_07.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_09; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_034_10, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 29A-1-38, scene of Margot Lane in Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_10; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_034_09, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 29A-1-38
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_11; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_034_11, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 29-4-26, scene of Lamont Cranston and Detective Harris talking in Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29 from CC 869, Take 2), 03/08/1954; street_smith_034_12; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 4) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_034_11, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 29-4-26.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29), 1954; street_smith_035_01; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 6) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_035_02, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 20-1-33; scene of Detective Harris in Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29), 1954; street_smith_035_02; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 6) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_035_02, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 20-1-33.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29), 1954; street_smith_035_03; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 7) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_035_04, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 19B-2-30; scene of Lamont Cranston and Detective Harris talking in Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29), 1954; street_smith_035_04; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 7) wound together without a core, might be related to different scenes. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_035_03.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29), 1954; street_smith_035_05; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 8) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_035_06, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 20A-1-34; scene of Detective Harris in Cranston's office.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (20-29), 1954; street_smith_035_06; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 8) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined sound reel for street_smith_035_05, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 20A-1-34.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (30-39), 1954; street_smith_036_01; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film
    Picture and sound film fragments (total of 7) wound together without a core, related to the same scene. This is a combined picture reel for street_smith_036_02, for Antrim Prod. scene/take/sound number 37-5-?; scene of Alex Bromm and Lamont Cranston talking in Bromm's apartment.
  - The Shadow: The Case of the Cotton Kimono, Trims (30-39), 1954; street_smith_036_02; all film credits listed in street_smith_001; 35mm film